# PRASETYO **DENNY** WIBOWO

3801 Conshohocken Ave, Apt. 423, Philadelphia, PA 19131 | Cell: (267)-902-9942 | Email: indocoffee@gmail.com

## PROFILE:

Advanced web developer with 8 years of experience in developing website from the ground up. Extensive knowledge in PHP based CMS, including creating custom templates for both Wordpress and Joomla. Experienced in PHP framework such as Laravel and Codeigniter. Ability to manage multiple projects, and communicating with the client directly.

# **QUALIFICATIONS:**

**Web Development Core:** 

PHP, HTML, CSS, Less, SaSS, JavaScript, Jquery

PHP framework:

Laravel, CodeIgniter, Symfony

**Softwares:** 

Sublime Text, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Illustrator

CMS and E-commerce:

Wordpress, Joomla, Shopify, X-Cart

**Database Administration/DBMS:** 

MySQL, PostGRE, MS SQL, Oracle, SQLite

Other:

Git, Bootstrap, LAMP, WAMP, Apache, IIS, Cpanel, WHM

#### **EDUCATION:**

Bachelor degree in Computer Science, Sekolah Tinggi Teknik Surabaya, Indonesia 2005

#### WORK HISTORY:

• 2007- Current Website Developer and Project Manager, B2B Design Development, LLC.

• 2006-2007 Freelance coder and web developer.

• 2005-2006 **IT Division Manager**, Pt. Drupadi Agung Lestari.

#### **COMPETENCIES:**

- Strong Analytical and problem-solving skills.
- A fast learner and a hard worker.
- Ability to work under pressure, both individually and collectively.

### PORTFOLIO:

• www.pwibowo.xyz/index.php#myWork

References and programming portfolio available upon request.